=Godslayer=
(Adapted from the novel Godslayer.)
(Divine Era, Lunisolar Calendar,
Emei Day)
The Ministry of Rites reports:
(Heavenly Law Bureau in the Capital)
The ore supply for Yuyou's porcelain
kilns is running low again.
The half-monsters in the Undercity have
been working day and night in shifts,
but it's still not enough.
May we send another batch of workers?
How many living sacrifices remain
in the Undercity?
The number of registered monster slaves
is over 2,300.
Which village has offered
the least tribute this year?
Shinian Village on the edge of Dazedi.
Then withdraw their protection.
Select the strongest ones
and send them to the Undercity
to ease the gods' burden.
Yes.
That boy from Dazedi,
how is he?
He's been on the road for some time.
He should have reached Shitu Forest
by now.
Lili's weakness
is about 3 cun below the neck,
[*8 centimeters]
right in the center of its chest.
Duo Mu,
hold off its left side.
Hahaha!
Yan!
Here it is!
No!
(Lili.)
(3 cun below the neck.)
[*8 centimeters]
(One.)
(Two.)
(Three.)
Kid,
we told you to cover our rear,
not strike it head-on.
Do you know
if your blade had missed by just a bit,
it would've turned around and gored you.
My aim never misses.
Listen,
this escort run
is only to get you to the Capital.
We don't have time to risk our lives
with you.
The Monster Wastes are deadly.
If you keep acting recklessly,
we won't be responsible for you.
Enough.
Stop arguing.
My sister is still waiting for me.
Is there any way
to cross the Monster Wastes faster?
Through Haogui Cave.
It's the shortest route.
Yan.
There are many Haogui creatures there.
If we provoke them,
we may not survive.
I have an idea.
Haogui follow their young master.
Wherever the young master goes,
the Haogui follow.
During the day, while they're asleep,
we steal the young master
and carry it away on a Bo beast.
When the Haogui wake up,
they'll chase after it.
We'll use that chance to pass through.
Yan,
it's up to you.
So these are Haogui?
Where is the young master?
Haogui always leave the best spot
for their young master.
It should be on the highest stalactite.
Someone took it.
And it happened not long ago.
What?
Why did they leave?
Forget it. We need to move.
While the Haogui are gone,
let's get through.
Looks like we're lucky.
I'll call the Bo here.
We need to hurry.
Wait.
(East; Gathering)
The Porcelain Armored Soldiers
are controlling the young master.
only serve the Capital.
Why would they be here?
Duo Mu.
Listen to what they're saying.
(Food.)
They said "food".
(Shinian Village.)
The food is in Shinian Village.
They're going to Shinian Village
to hunt.
Not to hunt.
It's...
(East; Gathering)
monsterization!
The Porcelain Armored Soldiers
are sending Haogui into the village
to bite the villagers
and infect them with monster aura,
turning them into half-monsters.
But Shinian Village
is protected by Heaven's barrier.
How could they get inside?
Look.
The protection has been withdrawn.
Let's go.
(Heaven punishment has come.)
The gods are punishing us.
They're here to hunt.
The villagers are the prey.
Haogui are the hounds.
The Porcelain Armored Soldiers
are the hunters.
They withdrew the protection,
lured the Haogui here,
turned the villagers into half-monsters,
and will take them back
to the Undercity.
So,
there was never any Heavenly punishment.
It was all their scheme.
We have to go.
The Haogui have finally been drawn away.
This is our best chance
to leave Haogui Cave.
But if we leave,
what about them?
You want to help them?
How?
There are thousands of Haogui.
Your sister is still waiting for you.
Xiaoyue.
Help!
Save us!
Mother.
Why did the gods take away
our protection?
We must not have offered
enough devotion.
The gods are angry.
They're punishing us.
But we gave them our finest grain.
We gave them our winter furs.
Even the hen that laid eggs
for our family.
We gave them everything we had.
Why are the gods still angry?
What does Redtail exist for?
(For every child in this world)
(to hold their own lives
in their hands.)
Yan.
What do you say?
I'll follow your lead.
Lu Yuanqing.
Your life has already been pledged
to the agency.
Until the escort is complete,
no one takes you away.
Yan.
We can't keep fighting like this.
There are too many Haogui.
Take down the leader first.
The young master is controlling
the Haogui.
Capture it,
and the rest will scatter.
Right.
Clear a path for me.
Come here, little one.
I will play with you.
(Who do you think you're
looking down on?)
(East; Gathering)
Leave the Porcelain Armored Soldiers
to me.
(Miss, don't kill me.)
(I want to go home.)
(Go home!)
That's it?
You're not so tough after all.
(It can revive?)
Then what do we do?
The back of its neck.
All the runes converge at the neck.
(Made in Yuyou Village)
We must cut through its neck completely.
Only then will the runes disappear.
I'll do it.
(Dust Rises, Duo Mu Awakens!)
(Wind Still, Yan Jiu Bind!)
(Turbid Dragon.)
(Second Strike.)
(Fish-Dragon Dance.)
Lu Yuanqing.
(Made in Yuyou Village)
Kid.
Nice teamwork.
This is your reward.
What's wrong with him?
The monster aura is rebelling.
It's entered his heart meridians.
Mother.
Who are they?
They saved us.
Are they gods?
Hey!
(The Nameless)
Thank you!
=Episode 3=
Heroes without names!